kehalim.com 2019-03-24

# Privacy Policy

Thanks for using our products and services ("Services"). These Services are provided by Kehalim Ltd. ("We", "Company"), registered at 16B Arlozorov St., Ra'anana Israel.  

Some Services include collecting user data. Most of this data is non-identifiable but some of it identifiable and so we want to be very clear about the purposes for collecting this data and the ways it is being used.

There are three touch points in which data may be collected:

## 1\. Our Websites

Non-identifiable information is collected when visitors enter our websites. This information may include IP address, browser and operating system types, pages visited and other statistical data. We collect this data to learn more about the way users interact with the site and help improve it.

## 2\. Our Services

Non-identifiable information may be collected on users of our Services. This information may include IP address, browser and operating system types, page visited, merchants, campaigns and ads interacted with and other statistical data. We collect this data to count and analyze usage of our Services, optimize and improve our Services and develop new Services.

## 3\. Our Console

When registering to Services, opening an account on our website or contacting us, you agree to provide personally identifiable information such as name, address, telephone number and email address. We use this information to guarantee secured entry to our Console and to contact you with information about our Services. Users who register to our paid Services are also requested to provide payment information, such as credit card details.

## Use of Cookies

In all three touch points we are using cookies to collect non-identifiable information. You may block cookies if you choose to, but it might affect some of our websites’ functionality. Please refer to your browser settings to see how cookies can be filtered or blocked.

## Third party services

We are using third party services such as Google Analytics and DoubleClick to help us in our marketing and advertising efforts. They help us advertise our products and reach, target and re-target relevant users. Each of these services provides information on their privacy, security, data collection and distribution policies on their own websites.

## Sharing Information

We are not in the business of selling personally identifiable information. We consider this information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. However, we may disclose personally identifiable information if required to do so by law to comply with a legal obligation, protect or defend our rights or protect against legal liability.

## Email communication and support requests

Periodically, we may choose to send news, bulletins, educational materials, marketing materials, or other information to you, and will use personally identifiable information to send such communications.

## Security

We take all reasonable steps to protect personally identifiable information and prevent such information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet or e-mail transmission is ever fully secure or error free, please keep this in mind.

## Policy Updates

We may, from time to time, update this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to periodically review this page be informed of changes. Your continued use of our Websites, Services or Platform after such modifications indicates your agreement with the modified Privacy Policy.

**Updated: Aug-11, 2016**
